pomelofashion.com 2014-12-03

# Privacy Policy - Pomelo

We at Pomelo ("Pomelo," "we," "us," or "our") know that our users ("you," "your," or "yourself") care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our Privacy Policy. By visiting or using the www.pomelofashion.com website and domain name, any other linked pages, features, content, and any other services we offer from time to time in connection with any of the foregoing (collectively, the "Website"), you agree to the practices and policies set forth in this Privacy Policy, and you hereby acknowledge and consent to our collection, use, and sharing of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Capitalized terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy have the meaning given to them in our Terms and Conditions of Use.

###  **WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?**

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that we gather when you are accessing or using our Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage, even if you have accessed the websites or services of those companies through our Website.

We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Services (as that term is defined in our Terms and conditions of Use). If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for the Services or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to us or on the Services. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [customerlove@pomelofashion.com](mailto:customerlove@pomelofashion.com).

###  **WHAT INFORMATION DOES** **POMELO** **COLLECT?**

We gather various types of Personal Information from our users, as explained more fully below. We may use this Personal Information to, among other things, personalize and improve our services, allow our users to set up a user account and profile, contact users, fulfill your requests for certain products and services, analyze how users utilize the Website, or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy. We may share certain types of Personal Information with third parties (as described in this Section and in Section III below). We collect the following types of information:

####  **Information You Provide to Us:**

We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us. We may also collect information you supply to us regarding your personal preferences and interests. If you access the Service through Facebook Connect, you understand that some content and/or information in your Facebook account (“Third Party Account Information”) may be transmitted into your account with us if you authorize such transmissions, and that Third Party Account Information transmitted to our Services is covered by this Privacy Policy. You can choose not to provide us with any or all of the information we specify or request, but then you may not be able to register with us or to take advantage of some or all of our features.

####  **Information Collected Automatically:**

Whenever you interact with our Website, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, “cookie” information, and the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or device that allow us to recognize your browser or device and tell us how and when pages in our Website are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or device to prevent or limit your computer’s or device’s acceptance of cookies, but doing so may prevent you from taking advantage of our Website’s best features. Our advertising partners may transmit cookies to your computer or device when you click on ads that appear on our site. This Privacy Policy does not cover cookies delivered to you by any of our advertisers.

When we collect usage information, we only use such data in aggregate form, in a manner that assures your anonymity. We may provide this aggregate usage information to our partners; our partners may use such information to understand how often and in what ways people use our Website, so that our partners, too, can endeavor to provide you with an optimal online experience.

####   **E-mail and Other Communications:**

We may contact you, by email or other means. If you do not want to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate your preference by changing your account accordingly. 

####  **WILL** **POMELO** **SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?**

We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information in personally identifiable form to anyone. We share your Personal Information in personally identifiable form with third parties only as described below:

####  **Affiliated Businesses and Third Party Websites We Do Not Control:**

In certain situations, businesses or third party websites we’re affiliated with may sell items or provide services to you through the Website (either alone or jointly with us). You can recognize when an affiliated business is associated with such a transaction or service, and we will share your Personal Information with that affiliated business only to the extent that we deem it related to such transaction or service. One such service may include the ability for you to automatically transmit information from your Pomelo account to an account on a third party website or service, such as Facebook. We have no control over the policies and practices of third party websites or businesses as to privacy or anything else, so if you choose to take part in any transaction or service relating to an affiliated website or business, please review all such business’s or websites’ policies.

####  **Agents:**

We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we inform you otherwise, our agents do not have any right to use the Personal Information we share with them beyond what we deem necessary to assist us in performing such tasks.

####  **Business Transfers:**

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information (which may include your Personal Information) is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Also, if we are acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, Personal Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

####  **Protection of** **Pomelo** **and Others:**

We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with laws; enforce or apply our conditions of use and/or other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Pomelo, our employees, our users, or others. We may exchange information with other companies and organizations (including governmental authorities) for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

####  **With Your Consent:**

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

###  **IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?**

Your account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. If you access your account via Facebook Connect, you may have additional or different sign-on protections through Facebook. You need to prevent unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password (or other sign-on protections) appropriately and limiting access to your computer or device by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

We attempt to protect the privacy of your account and other Personal Information we hold in our records, but we cannot guarantee complete security. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

The Website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When following a link to another site you should read that site’s privacy policy.

###  **WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION CAN I ACCESS?**

Through your account settings, you may access, and, in some cases, edit or delete the following information you’ve provided to us:

  * name and password
  * email address
  * shipping and billing information
  * user profile information and User Content, including images you have uploaded to the site.

The information you can view and update may change as the Website changes. If you have any questions about viewing or updating information we have on file about you, please contact us at [customerlove@pomelofashion.com](mailto:customerlove@pomelofashion.com).

###  **WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?**

You can always elect not to disclose information to us. However, please keep in mind that we may need some information to allow you register with us or to take advantage of some or all of our features, and if you choose not to provide that information, your ability to use our Website and services may be limited.

You may be able to add, update, or delete information. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your account by visiting your account settings. Please note that some information may remain in our private records after your deletion of such information from your account. We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information even if you update or delete it, but we will not use that information in a manner that would identify you personally.

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please change your account settings accordingly. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

###  **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or contacting you directly via email or other means. You are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when you use the Website after such changes have been first posted.

###  **QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policies, please send us a detailed message to [customerlove@pomelofashion.com](mailto:customerlove@pomelofashion.com). We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
